https://www.becanada.com/internet/1601262397/privacy.html

*** Perfectraffic.com ***
-- Worldwide, Social, Seo and Targeted traffic services.
*** Shopperbot.net ***
-- Real Time Compare / save on millions of items.
- Power Submitter Software (classifieds/all)
- Affiliates Area / Login
- Affiliate Program (FREE)
- Becanada 'net 101 NEWS'Ls (FREE)
- Refund / Cancelation Policies
- Terms Of Service (Website)
- Website Automated Promotion
- Direct Targeted Traffic (300+ categories, 100+ countries) -
- US SEO Traffic
- All In One Traffic
- Traffic Specials (Save 40%!)
- Targeted Traffic
- US Mobile Targeted Traffic
- Alexa Traffic (www or by country)
- Speciality Traffic (Casino, Adult)
- Search Engines and SEO Marketing
- Websites I Select...
- How To, Marketing Resources -
- 10000+ Free Classifieds Listings(Updates daily, new sites hourly)
- Top Free Directories, Free Social Sites.
- 75 Internet Marketing Channels(Over 50,000 Articles, updates daily)
- 100000 Online Resources(20 sections)
- Add Url / Link / Resource
- Add Classifieds Site
- Add Article (becanada.com)
- View/Post Free Classified Ad[s]
- View/Post Link[s] in Free Top Directories, Social Sites.
TOOLS: LSN Systems / Free Leads
NEW: Cashlinks 3 ...
- What is Cashlinks?
- Do First?
- 10 ways to make Money?
- I Got a website...
- I Got no website ...
How Do I Increase Traffic And Sales Using:
Email Follow ups
Targeted Traffic:
All In One Traffic
How Do I Increase and/or Automate:
Webmaster profits
Becanada Privacy Policy:
Becanada has been in business now for over
15 years and has 1000s of clients worldwide. Becanada is committed to creating
and selling quality products and services and supporting said products and
services with prompt support service. These policies apply to ALL Becanada
products and services; including all sites/services owned by or sold by Becanada
directly. If you have ANY questions about these policies and/or any other
questions ; including questions about our products/services - please
contact us.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order,
subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked
to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You
may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following
ways:
; To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
; To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information
and feedback we receive from you)
; To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service
requests and support needs)
; To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without
your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased
product or service requested.
; To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you
information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving
occasional company news, updates, related product or service information,
etc.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access
your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information
is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted
into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those
authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep
the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security
numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that
enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser
and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping
cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile
aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer
better site experiences and tools in the future.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally
identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who
assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing
you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate
to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others
rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor
information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising,
or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products
or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent
privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the
content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect
the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to
be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore
will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without
your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our
site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into
their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' , 'Members Area', 'Login'
or 'Customer Login' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy
Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years
of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who
are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through
our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use,
disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website
at terms of service
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our
websites privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on
this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact
us using the information below.
Free Privacy Policy
"Automating Your Online Business, Online Advertising, Website Marketing & Activities In Less Time, Easily - Helping You get more done in less time with better results from start to finish... for over 15 years."
Newest Internet Marketing Training and How To's From The Newsletters and Blog:
"Rotating Ads [html/text/other] at your Classifieds to increase sales and results."
"WHICH OF THESE WORDS ATTRACT YOUR CLIENTS -  By Charlie Cook,charliecook.net"
"Eight Basic Opt-in List Building Techniques To Grow Your Business by Joe Reinbold, homebizlink.com"
"Increasing sales/leads/traffic by email using the ISell Classifieds at your website[s]."
"Affiliate Marketing Online - 7 Quick Approach To Increase Targeted Traffic Today"
"How to Use Affiliate Marketing Online To Accomplish Economic Freedom"
For More Of These - Click here
Join Our Free Newsletter:
More Newsletters
Contact Sales / Support:
EMail: Click here To Contact Us
Phone: 613-836-6389 (Mon-Fri 10am-5pm Eastern)
Mailing Address:
D.B. Software Ent. INC
195 Spruce Ridge Road , Carp,
Ontario , K0A 1L0, Canada
(20 Minutes West Of Ottawa, Canada's Capital City.)
Website Replication:
Website Replication Technology [click here for information to get your own site replicated]
By Becanada - Used by over 1,000,000 affiliates daily worldwide ; including this website. First affiliate / replication software in 1996.
Shopping Cart :
Cart : no items View / Checkout - Click Here
Return to top of page | Homepage | Newsletter | Affiliate Programs | About Us | Coming Soon... | Privacy Policy | Terms of Service (website)
Report all incidents of spam by clicking on "NO SPAM" image - include complete email received by you. Becanada has a ZERO spam tolerance. Members that spam are subject to fines and legal action.
Copyright 1996-2020 Becanada.com / D.B. Software Ent. INC - No part of this site may be reproduced without express permission.
